<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="105">
	<author>Rockstar</author>

	<version>1.0.0.5</version>

	<title>
		<en>Additional Game Settings</en>
		<de>Zusätzliche Spieleinstellungen</de>
		<fr>Paramètres De Jeu Supplémentaires</fr>
		<pl>Dodatkowe Ustawienia Gry</pl>
		<ru>Дополнительные Настройки Игры</ru>
	</title>

	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[This mod adds a new settings tab to the pause menu.

Available functions:
- Enable/disable the interface,
- Change the interface color (custom colors can be added to the file ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/uiColors.xml"),
- Enable/disable the crosshair,
- Display a transition effect when switching cameras,
- Enable/disable unnecessary informational windows,
- Enable/disable blinking notifications,
- Enable/disable mouse camera movement in object placement mode,
- Enable/disable automatic game save start,
- Filter objects in the shop (all/base/mods/DLC),
- Toggle lighting from other maps (custom lighting can be added to the folder ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/lighting"),
- Smooth camera movements,
- Start the vehicle engine by pressing the acceleration key,
- Enable/disable depth of field (DoF),
- Enable/disable camera collision,
- Display the current date (customizable format/position/background/color/font boldness),
- Added "Quit to desktop" button.

Changelog 1.0.0.1:
- Added support for version 1.6.0.0 of the game,
- Added the ability to change the HUD color for mods: Courseplay, Enhanced Vehicle, Extended Game Info Display.

Changelog 1.0.0.2:
- Added an option to switch between walking and running mode (press and hold/press),
- Added an option to switch between walking and crouching mode (press and hold/press),
- Added the ability to choose a custom color for HUDs and the clock,
- Fixed clock HUD scaling.

Changelog 1.0.0.3:
- Fixed an issue with the unavailable HUD color change option,
- Fixed the error ".../AdditionalSettings.lua:1363: attempt to index nil with 'delete'".

Changelog 1.0.0.4:
- Fixed the function "Easier engine starting", which was not working after patch 1.7.0.0,
- Fixed an issue where the month name was displayed incorrectly on the clock (November instead of October),
- Added an option to run faster by double-pressing a key.

Changelog 1.0.0.5:
- Added tooltips for disabled interface options,
- Improved compatibility with some mods.]]></en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[Diese Mod fügt dem Pausenmenü einen neuen Einstellungstab hinzu.

Verfügbare Funktionen:
- Aktivieren/Deaktivieren der Benutzeroberfläche,
- Ändern der Benutzeroberflächenfarbe (benutzerdefinierte Farben können in der Datei ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/uiColors.xml" hinzugefügt werden),
- Aktivieren/Deaktivieren des Fadenkreuzes,
- Anzeigen eines Übergangseffekts beim Kamerawechsel,
- Aktivieren/Deaktivieren unnötiger Informationsfenster,
- Aktivieren/Deaktivieren blinkender Benachrichtigungen,
- Aktivieren/Deaktivieren der Maus-Kamerabewegung im Objektplatzierungsmodus,
- Aktivieren/Deaktivieren des automatischen Spielstarts bei Speichern,
- Objekte im Shop filtern (alle/Basis/Mods/DLC),
- Beleuchtung von anderen Karten ein-/ausschalten (benutzerdefinierte Beleuchtung kann im Ordner ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/lighting" hinzugefügt werden),
- Kamerabewegungen glätten,
- Fahrzeugmotor durch Drücken der Beschleunigungstaste starten,
- Aktivieren/Deaktivieren der Tiefenschärfe (DoF),
- Aktivieren/Deaktivieren der Kamerakollision,
- Aktuelles Datum anzeigen (anpassbares Format/Position/Hintergrund/Farbe/Schriftstärke),
- Ein "Zum Desktop zurückkehren"-Button wurde hinzugefügt.

Changelog 1.0.0.1:
- Unterstützung für Version 1.6.0.0 des Spiels hinzugefügt,
- Möglichkeit zur Änderung der HUD-Farbe für die Mods hinzugefügt: Courseplay, Enhanced Vehicle, Extended Game Info Display.

Changelog 1.0.0.2:
- Eine Option zum Umschalten zwischen Geh-und Laufmodus wurde hinzugefügt (drücken und halten/drücken),
- Eine Option zum Umschalten zwischen Geh-und Hockmodus wurde hinzugefügt (drücken und halten/drücken),
- Die Möglichkeit hinzugefügt, eine benutzerdefinierte Farbe für HUDs und die Uhr auszuwählen,
- Skalierung des Uhr-HUDs behoben.

Changelog 1.0.0.3:
- Ein Problem mit der nicht verfügbaren HUD-Farbänderungsoption wurde behoben,
- Fehler ".../AdditionalSettings.lua:1363: attempt to index nil with 'delete'" wurde behoben.

Changelog 1.0.0.4:
- Die Funktion "Einfacherer Motorstart", die nach Patch 1.7.0.0 nicht funktionierte, wurde behoben,
- Ein Problem wurde behoben, bei dem der Monatsname auf der Uhr falsch angezeigt wurde (November statt Oktober),
- Eine Option zum schnelleren Laufen durch doppeltes Drücken einer Taste wurde hinzugefügt.

Changelog 1.0.0.5:
- Hinweise für deaktivierte Schnittstellenoptionen hinzugefügt,
- Verbesserte Kompatibilität mit einigen Mods.]]></de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[Ce mod ajoute un nouvel onglet de paramètres au menu pause.

Fonctions disponibles :
- Activer/désactiver l'interface utilisateur,
- Modifier la couleur de l'interface utilisateur (des couleurs personnalisées peuvent être ajoutées dans le fichier ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/uiColors.xml"),
- Activer/désactiver le réticule,
- Afficher un effet de transition lors du changement de caméra,
- Activer/désactiver les fenêtres d'information inutiles,
- Activer/désactiver les notifications clignotantes,
- Activer/désactiver le mouvement de la caméra par la souris en mode placement d'objets,
- Activer/désactiver le lancement automatique du jeu après sauvegarde,
- Filtrer les objets dans la boutique (tous/de base/mods/DLC),
- Activer/désactiver l'éclairage d'autres cartes (des éclairages personnalisés peuvent être ajoutés dans le dossier ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/lighting"),
- Lisser les mouvements de la caméra,
- Démarrer le moteur du véhicule en appuyant sur la touche d'accélération,
- Activer/désactiver la profondeur de champ (DoF),
- Activer/désactiver la collision de la caméra,
- Afficher la date actuelle (format/position/fond/couleur/épaisseur de police personnalisables),
- Un bouton "Retourner au bureau" a été ajouté.

Changelog 1.0.0.1:
- Prise en charge de la version 1.6.0.0 du jeu,
- Ajout de la possibilité de changer la couleur du HUD pour les mods : Courseplay, Enhanced Vehicle, Extended Game Info Display.

Changelog 1.0.0.2:
- Ajout d'une option pour basculer entre le mode marche et course (appuyer et maintenir/appuyer),
- Ajout d'une option pour basculer entre le mode marche et accroupi (appuyer et maintenir/appuyer),
- Ajout de la possibilité de choisir une couleur personnalisée pour les HUD et l'horloge,
- Correction de l'échelle du HUD de l'horloge.

Changelog 1.0.0.3:
- Correction d’un problème avec l’option de changement de couleur du HUD indisponible.
- Correction de l'erreur ".../AdditionalSettings.lua:1363: attempt to index nil with 'delete'".

Changelog 1.0.0.4:
- Correction de la fonction "Démarrage moteur simplifié" qui ne fonctionnait plus après le patch 1.7.0.0,
- Correction d’un problème où le nom du mois s’affichait incorrectement sur l’horloge (novembre au lieu d’octobre),
- Une option pour courir plus vite en appuyant deux fois sur une touche a été ajoutée.

Changelog 1.0.0.5:
- Ajout d’info-bulles pour les options d’interface désactivées,
- Compatibilité améliorée avec certains mods.]]></fr>
		<pl>
			<![CDATA[Ten mod dodaje zakładkę z nowymi ustawieniami do menu pauzy.

Dostępne funkcje:
- Włączanie/wyłączanie interfejsu,
- Zmiana koloru interfejsu (można dodać własne kolory do pliku ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/uiColors.xml"),
- Włączanie/wyłączanie celownika,
- Wyświetlanie efektu przejścia przy zmianie kamer,
- Włączanie/wyłączanie zbędnych okien informacyjnych,
- Włączanie/wyłączanie migających powiadomień,
- Włączanie/wyłączanie przesuwania kamery myszą w trybie stawiania obiektów,
- Włączanie/wyłączanie automatycznego startu zapisu gry,
- Filtrowanie obiektów w sklepie (wszystkie/podstawowe/mody/dlc),
- Przełączanie oświetlenia z innych map (można dodać własne oświetlenie do folderu ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/lighting"),
- Wygładzanie ruchów kamery,
- Uruchamianie silnika pojazdu przez naciśnięcie przycisku przyspieszenia,
- Włączanie/wyłączanie głębi ostrości (DoF),
- Włączanie/wyłączanie kolizji kamery,
- Wyświetlanie bieżącej daty (możliwość dostosowania formatu/pozycji/tła/koloru/pogrubienia czcionki),
- Dodano przycisk "Wyjdź do pulpitu".

Changelog 1.0.0.1:
- Dodano wsparcie dla wersji 1.6.0.0 gry,
- Dodano możliwość zmiany koloru HUD dla modów: Courseplay, Enhanced Vehicle, Extended Game Info Display.

Changelog 1.0.0.2:
- Dodano opcje przełączania między trybem chodzenia i biegania (naciśnij i przytrzymaj/naciśnij),
- Dodano opcje przełączania między trybem chodzenia i kucania (naciśnij i przytrzymaj/naciśnij),
- Dodano możliwość wyboru niestandardowego koloru dla HUD-ów i zegara,
- Naprawiono skalowanie HUD zegara.

Changelog 1.0.0.3:
- Naprawiono problem z niedostepną opcją zmiany koloru HUD-ów,
- Naprawiono błąd ".../AdditionalSettings.lua:1363: attempt to index nil with 'delete'".

Changelog 1.0.0.4:
- Naprawiono funkcję "Uproszczone uruchamianie silnika", która nie działała po patchu 1.7.0.0,
- Naprawiono problem z niepoprawnym wyświetlaniem nazwy miesiąca (listopad zamiast październik ) na zegarze,
- Dodano opcję szybszego biegania po podwójnym naciśnięciu klawisza.

Changelog 1.0.0.5:
- Dodano podpowiedzi dla wyłączonych opcji interfejsu,
- Poprawiono kompatybilność z niektórymi modami.]]></pl>
		<ru>
			<![CDATA[Этот мод добавляет новую вкладку настроек в меню паузы.

Доступные функции:
- Включение/отключение пользовательского интерфейса,
- Изменение цвета пользовательского интерфейса (настраиваемые цвета можно добавить в файл ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/uiColors.xml"),
- Включение/отключение прицела,
- Отображение эффекта перехода при смене камеры,
- Включение/отключение ненужных информационных окон,
- Включение/отключение мигающих уведомлений,
- Включение/отключение движения камеры с помощью мыши в режиме размещения объектов,
- Включение/отключение автоматического запуска игры после сохранения,
- Фильтрация объектов в магазине (все/основные/моды/DLC),
- Включение/отключение освещения с других карт (настраиваемое освещение можно добавить в папку ".../modSettings/FS25_additionalGameSettings/lighting"),
- Сглаживание движений камеры,
- Запуск двигателя транспортного средства нажатием кнопки ускорения,
- Включение/отключение глубины резкости (DoF),
- Включение/отключение столкновений камеры,
- Отображение текущей даты (настраиваемый формат/позиция/фон/цвет/толщина шрифта),
- Добавлена ​​кнопка "Выйти на рабочий стол".

Changelog 1.0.0.1:
- Добавлена поддержка версии 1.6.0.0 игры,
- Добавлена возможность изменения цвета HUD для модов: Courseplay, Enhanced Vehicle, Extended Game Info Display.

Changelog 1.0.0.2:
- Добавлена опция переключения между режимами ходьбы и бега (нажать и удерживать/нажать),
- Добавлена опция переключения между режимами ходьбы и приседания (нажать и удерживать/нажать),
- Добавлена возможность выбора пользовательского цвета для HUD-ов и часов,
- Исправлено масштабирование HUD часов.

Changelog 1.0.0.3:
- Исправлена проблема с недоступной опцией изменения цвета HUD,
- Исправлена ошибка ".../AdditionalSettings.lua:1363: attempt to index nil with 'delete'".

Changelog 1.0.0.4:
- Исправлена функция "Упрощённый запуск двигателя", не работавшая после патча 1.7.0.0,
- Исправлена ошибка, из-за которой на часах некорректно отображалось название месяца (ноябрь вместо октября),
- Добавлена опция быстрого бега при двойном нажатии клавиши.

Changelog 1.0.0.5:
- Добавлены подсказки для отключённых параметров интерфейса,
- Улучшена совместимость с некоторыми модами.]]></ru>
	</description>

	<iconFilename>icon_additionalGameSettings.png</iconFilename>

	<multiplayer supported="true"/>

	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/utils/AdditionalSettingsUtil.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/AdditionalSettingsManager.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/AdditionalSettings.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/gui/AdditionalSettingsGui.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/gui/AdditionalSettingsPage.lua"/>
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<l10n filenamePrefix="localization/l10n"/>
</modDesc>