<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="109" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://validation.gdn.giants-software.com/xml/fs25/modDesc.xsd">
  <author>Evan Kirsch</author>
  <version>1.1.0.2</version>
  <title>
      <en>Net Worth Tracker</en>
      <de>Vermögens-Tracker</de>
  </title>
  <description>
    <en><![CDATA[
Adds menu screen with a tab to sumarize your farms total value in a balance sheet and a history tab to summaries the history of your farms value.

Farm Value:
This is the summary of the current day's farm value. Each line item in the balance sheet contains a name, catagory, additional details and a value and are sortable by name, catagory and value.
The line items are summaized into four subtotals:
  - Cash: cash and loans
  - Equipment
  - Property: land and buildings
  - Inventory: fill and livestock

Farm Value History:
This is a history of farm values recorded at the end of each day. Each line item notes a day and the value of the farm at the end of the day. It is sortable by date.

Dev Console Commands:
  - `nwtBuildHistory` - rebuilds fake value history from previous day
  - `nwtToggleDebug` - toggles debug mode for the mod
  - `nwtGetFarmValue` - calculates the current farm value
  - `nwtFarmValueToCSV <file location>` - exports the farms current value to CSV. Optional param of the absolute file location of the file to be saved. The defualt save location is `<save game location>/nwt_farm_value.csv`
  - `nwtFarmValueHistoryToCSV <file location>` - exports the farms value history to CSV. Optional param of the absolute file location of the file to be saved. The defualt save location is `<save game location>/nwt_famr_value_history.csv`

GitHub link: https://github.com/EvanKirsch/fs25_nwt

Changelog
---
1.1.0.2:
  - Corrects animal value when health or fitness is less than 100%
  - Fixes error when generating files before game has been saved
1.1.0.1:
  - Adds PL translation
  - Removes GIANTS `Object` superclass from instantiated data objects to reduce object clutter resulting in reduced server performance
1.1.0.0:
  - Adds Farm Value History tab
  - Adds console commands `nwtBuildHistory`, `nwtToggleDebug`, `nwtGetFarmValue`, `nwtFarmValueToCSV`, `nwtFarmValueHistoryToCSV`
1.0.0.2:
  - Updates German translations
  - Adds multiplayer support
1.0.0.1:
  - Initial release
    ]]></en>
    <de><![CDATA[
Fügt einen Menübildschirm mit einer Registerkarte zur Zusammenfassung des Gesamtwerts Ihrer Farm in einer Bilanz und einer Registerkarte "Verlauf" zur Zusammenfassung der Wertentwicklung Ihrer Farm hinzu.

Bauernhof Wert:
Jeder Bilanzposten enthält einen Namen, eine Kategorie, zusätzliche Details und einen Wert und kann nach Name, Kategorie und Wert sortiert werden.
Die Posten werden in vier Zwischensummen zusammengefasst:
  - Bargeld: Bargeld und Darlehen
  - Ausrüstung
  - Eigentum: Ackerland und Gebäude
  - Inventar: Füllmittel und Viehbestand

Hofwertgeschichte:
Dies ist eine Übersicht der landwirtschaftlichen Betriebswerte, die jeweils am Ende eines Tages erfasst wurden. Jeder Eintrag enthält den entsprechenden Tag und den Wert des Betriebs am Ende des Tages. Die Daten sind nach Datum sortierbar.

Befehle für die Entwicklerkonsole:
  - `nwtBuildHistory` – Stellt den simulierten Wertverlauf des Vortages wieder her.
  - `nwtToggleDebug` – Aktiviert/Deaktiviert den Debug-Modus für die Mod.
  - `nwtGetFarmValue` – Berechnet den aktuellen Wert der Farm.
  - `nwtFarmValueToCSV <Dateipfad>` – Exportiert den aktuellen Wert der Farm als CSV-Datei. Optionaler Parameter: Absoluter Dateipfad der zu speichernden Datei. Standardmäßig wird die Datei unter `<Spielstandverzeichnis>/nwt_farm_value.csv` gespeichert.
  - `nwtFarmValueHistoryToCSV <Dateipfad>` – Exportiert den Wertverlauf der Farm als CSV-Datei. Optionaler Parameter: Absoluter Dateipfad der zu speichernden Datei. Standardmäßig wird die Datei unter `<Spielstandverzeichnis>/nwt_farm_value_history.csv` gespeichert.

GitHub-Link: https://github.com/EvanKirsch/fs25_nwt

Änderungsprotokoll
---
1.1.0.2:
  - Korrigiert den Tierwert, wenn Gesundheit oder Fitness unter 100% liegen.
  - Behebt einen Fehler beim Generieren von Dateien, bevor das Spiel gespeichert wurde.
1.1.0.1:
  - Fügt pl-Übersetzung hinzu
  - Entfernt die GIANTS `Object` aus instanziierten Datenobjekten, um die Objektanzahl zu reduzieren und dadurch die Serverleistung zu verringern.
1.1.0.0:
  - Fügt die Registerkarte Hofwertgeschichte hinzu
  - Fügt Konsolenbefehle `nwtBuildHistory`, `nwtToggleDebug`, `nwtGetFarmValue`, `nwtFarmValueToCSV`, `nwtFarmValueHistoryToCSV` hinzu
1.0.0.2:
  - Deutsche Übersetzungen aktualisiert
  - Mehrspielerunterstützung hinzugefügt
1.0.0.1:
  - Erste Veröffentlichung
    ]]></de>
  </description>    
  <iconFilename>icon_NetWorthTracker.dds</iconFilename>
  <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />
  <multiplayer supported="true"/>
  <extraSourceFiles>
    <sourceFile filename="src/NWT_netWorthTracker.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/NWT_historyManager.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/dao/NWT_historyDao.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/dev/NWT_console.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/gui/NWT_inGameMenuNetWorthTracker.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/gui/NWT_historyDelegate.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/gui/NWT_farmValueDelegate.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/model/NWT_entry.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/model/NWT_history.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/util/NWT_csvUtil.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/util/NWT_fillCalcUtil.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/util/NWT_historyUtil.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="src/util/NWT_netWorthCalcUtil.lua" />
  </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
